嗨，大家好，欢迎来到estoir的拍摄演示。
hey everyone welcome to the shot presentation of estoir
所以，是的，你把它读成estoir
so yeah you pronounce it estoir
它是法国的欺诈或故事
it's French fraud or story
我们很喜欢车辆系统中的法国名字
we quite like French name in the vehicle system
或者是一个大计划的一部分，使你自己的法语
or part of a big plan to make your own French
总之
anyway
什么是所有的东西是写故事的工具
what is all about istwa is a tool to write stories
但什么是故事
but what is a story
一个故事就是一组小的UA
so a story is just a small set of UA
一个故事就是在一个很好的相关环境中显示的一小部分UA组件
components displayed in a nice related environment
这种方式有很多好处
and this kind of a lot of benefits
例如
for example
当你想为你的应用程序击败某种组件时
when you want to beat some kind of component
的时候
for your application
你不必考虑上下文的问题
you don't have to mind of the context
可以将组件提取到一个故事中
can extract the component to a story
然后专注于你所构建的功能
then focus on the features your building
而不用考虑集成的问题
without mining about the integration
当一切完成后
and when everything's done
你可以
you can
将你的组件重新导入你的应用程序中
import your components back into your application
任何你想要的地方
anywhere you want
另一个很酷的好处是，你有
another cool benefit is that you have
所有的组件
all your components
组织在集中的库中
organizing the centralized library
这样，你的团队中的任何人
so that anyone in your team
都可以看到有哪些组件可供他们使用
can see what components are available to them
以及他们如何使用它
and how they can use it
因为你可以
because you can
记录你的组件的功能，以便于
document the features of your component so that
开发人员可以看到每个组件增加了哪些参数
developer can see what arguments each components add
和你的插槽，他们有
and you slot they have
并且他们可以实时地将这些值转化为
and they can twig these values
实时地
in real time
他们可以将这些值实时地加入到你的兄弟中，看他们如何反应
right into your brothers to see how they react
你还可以利用这些组件的不同使用情况，展示一些
you can also showcase some
你还可以使用我们称之为 "勇气 "的东西来展示这些组件的不同用例。
different use cases of those components using
我们称之为Valiant
what we call valiant
最后，你可以测试你的组件
lastly you can test your components
这样你就能确保在开发过程中不会出现视觉上的调节
so that you make sure you don't have visual regulation
在开发过程中
during the development
你的应用程序，但当eastoil
of your application but when eastoil
有其他
there are other
框架的蓝索
framework to blue soys
是什么让你的旋转与他们不同
what make you swirl different from them
第一件事是什么
what the first thing
就是eastoil是原生的项目
is that eastoil is native to with projects
所以它的安装是非常容易的
so it's super easy to install
你只需要插入软件包
you just have to insert the package
就可以了，而且默认情况下它会
and by default it will
查找你的项目的vit配置文件
look up for the vit configuration file of your project
所以你可以让它工作
so you can make it work
无需任何配置
without any configuration whatsoever
它的速度也非常快，因为它使用的是vits
it's also blazing fast because it's using vits
所以你只有几秒钟的时间来启动
so you have mini seconds to start
牢房面纱
the cell veils
然后你有即时的自动视频
and then you have instant automatic videos
感谢视觉
thanks to vis
它也是超级z学习
it's also super z to learn
所以是
so is
基本上查看单一的5个组件，以点结束
basically view single 5 components ending with dot
酱油，几个
soy that a few
所以绝对不奇怪
so there's absolutely no surprise
你可以
you can
在文档网站上看到很多例子
see a lot of example on the documentation website
这也是视觉功能的复杂性
it's also the visual feature complex
因为你有一吨的功能
because you have 1t of features
来测试
to test the
响应式设计，测试你的自定义事件，保存
responsive design to test your custom events to save
子自定义状态，所以一切都准备好了，无需
sub custom states so everything is ready to use without
任何第三方的brigan和nasty的需要。
any need for any 3rd party brigan and nasty
它是1%的自定义之一
it's one of 1% custom
伊莎贝拉可以定制你的东亚应用的外观
Isabella can customize the look of
您的东亚战争应用程序，以便它可以匹配
your eastwar application so that it can match
你的品牌团队 你的乐队标志 任何东西
your brand team your band logo anything
这里有一个超级独立的例子
here's a super separate example
的故事文件
of a story file
你只需要把你的组件放在那里
where you just have to put your component there
就像在任何单一的战斗组件中一样
just like in any single fights components
如果你需要一个机架
and if you need a rack
态，你可以放上控制，这里有一个
if states you can put controls and there's a
这里有一个控制槽
controlled slots here
有一些预制的控制组件，如
and there are pre built controls components like
这个东部战争文本
this eastwar text
但你可以把任何东西放在另一个槽里
but you can put anything another slot
因此，让我向你展示一些好的功能从
so let me show you some of the good features from
eastwar的一些好功能，首先是最有用的功能
eastwar starting with the most useful features ever
黑暗模式
the dark mode
然后
then
你有一个搜索栏，可以快速访问你的商店
you have the search bar to quickly access your store
在这里，你有一个网格布局，其中有几个图标
here you have a grid layout with several valiants
如果你点击一个，你可以更新它
if you click on one you can update it
你可以看到
and you see that
它是自动反应在兄弟身上的
it's automatically reacting on the brother
当然，你可以
you can of course
当然，你可以复制粘贴生成的切面，将其直接用于
copy paste the generated cut to be used right
到你的应用程序中
into your application
你也可以注意到这一点，但这意味着
also you can notice this little but it's meaning that
这些
these
道具是由组件自动检测出来的
props are automatically detected from the component
所以你不需要手动创建这些道具
so you don't have to manually create those
然后你有很多控件来操作你的道具
then you have a lot of controls to manipulate
一些滑块，一些单选框
your props some kind of sliders some kind of radio
一些额外的选择
some kind of selects extra
你还可以保存这些状态
you can also save these states
更新的状态
the updated states
这样你就可以快速
so that you can quickly
在初始状态和
toggle between the initial states and
你刚刚保存的状态
the states you just save
如果你有某种有益的镶嵌物的话
if you have some kind of salutary insetups
是为了我们会产生一堆超级
is to our will generate a bunch of super
的文件。
sparkle documentation for white
你也可以写
you can also write
文档的
documentation for
故事写成markdown
stories in markdown
它将出现在这里
it will appear here
你可以测试你的组件的响应能力
you can test the responsiveness of your components
你认为这些滑块
you think these sliders
也有很多预设，可以改变你测试的分辨率。
and there's also a lot of presets to
改变你所测试的分辨率
change the resolution you're testing
还有一些事件，你可以在这里
there's also events that you canin
显示在这里，你可以改变背景颜色
display here you can change the background colors
你可以使用棋盘格
you can use checkerboard
有很多功能
there's 1t of features
我只有这么多时间来展示它们
I am only have so much time to show them all
所以我想我将在这里结束
so I think I would stop there
是时候了，我一直在用口香糖建造东边的房子。
time you go and I've been building east while with gum
事实是，你将90%的它，是真棒
and truth is you will 90% of it and is awesome
所以去赞助他们的吉他
so go sponsor em on guitar
也欢迎任何人为eastoil做出贡献。
also anyone up to contribute to eastoil is welcome
所以请随时加入我们的折扣
so feel free to join our discount
如果你想更深入地了解eastoil的情况
if you want to dive deeper into eastoil
请务必查看
be sure to check out
我们与Giume的第一次确认鹳
our first confirm stork with giume
我们将解释更多很酷的东西
we'll explain a lot more cool stuff
谢谢收听
thanks for listening